Arjun Solanki

Full Stack Web Developer

Well-qualified Full Stack Developer familiar with a wide range of programming utilities and languages. Knowledgeable of backend and frontend development requirements. Able to handle any part of the process with ease. Collaborative team player with excellent technical abilities offering 6 years of related experience.

Work History

2019-09 -Current

Full Stack Web Developer

Dignizant Technologies, Surat, Gujarat

- Coordinated with Full stack web developer to evaluate and improve software and hardware interfaces.
- Orchestrated efficient large-scale software deployments, including testing features and correcting code.
- Adjusted design parameters to boost performance and incorporate new features.
- · Reviewed code, debugged problems and corrected issues.

2018-05 -2019-07

Senior PHP Web Developer

Techno Brigade Infotech, Surat, Gujarat

- Coded websites using HTML, CSS, JavaScript and jQuery languages.
- Planned website development, converting mockups into usable web presence with HTML, JavaScript, AJAX and JSON coding.
- Established presentation consistency across Chrome, Safari, Firefox and other common browser interfaces.

2014-12 -2018-04

PHP Web Developer

Veer Infotech, Surat, Gujarat

- Worked closely with Project Managers and other developers to define parameters and plan detailed specifications with clear project deliverables and timelines to meet strict deadlines.
- Created web applications and components using PHP programming language.
- Performed troubleshooting of technical issues within production environment.

Education

2010-03 -2013-04 **Bachelor of Computer Applications**

Swaminarayn College Of Computer Science - Bhavnagar

Address

Contact

Surat, GJ, 395006

Phone

800 029 3623

E-mail

arjun.solankia703@gmail.com

Skills

Laravel

••••

React

••••

Angular Vue

••••

CSS

•••••

HTML

•••••

Nodejs

••••

CakePHP